"The Demons that Lurk in the Moonlight"
Coming straight at me--
is that all you can do?
If that's the case...
You'll never become
a full-fledged knight, Kasel.
What I'm trying to become
isn't a "full-fledged" knight!
I'm going to become a knight
that can protect everyone!
There he goes again.
Always with the big mouth!
Then you should at least be able to beat me!
You're too straightforward, Kasel.
That could cost you dearly.
Dammit!
You've still got a long way to go
before you can beat me.
I'm always one level above you.
You're just taller, that's it!
I'm going to jump over that...
...easily!
All right, time for work, Mr. Apprentice.
Gran, Flegg, you too--get to work.
I know.
Dang, so Clause wins again.
It won't be easy, obviously.
You owe me lunch, Flegg.
Come on, Kasel. You need be strong enough
to protect my lunch, at least.
That's not my concern.
You're honest and a hard worker,
we'll give you that.
Huh.
You just need to work on
your stamina and your technique.
I mean, you're not bad,
as far as apprentices go.
With Clause training you every day,
I'm sure you'll get stronger soon.
Okay, and thus, lunch is on you, Kasel.
How does that follow?!
You're just making stuff up!
So boring, as always.
Are you sure you want to be
saying that while on patrol?
It's fine. If we're bored,
that means it's peaceful.
Oh, how joyful it is to be bored!
But you don't have to announce it so loudly...
Oh, I know. I have to stop by May's place
to make sure nothing dangerous happened!
Hey, is that...
A dark elf.
What's a dark elf doing in Orvelia...?
That's unsettling.
Yes, what does he want?
You're Guardian Knights, aren't you?
Why won't you throw him out?
Huh? But he hasn't done anything wrong...
It's a dark elf! Obviously he's up to no good!
Yeah, they're like
the embodiment of bad omens.
Please, folks, stay calm. I'll make sure
my superiors know about this.
It's break time, right?
You go ahead and return.
Yes...
Don't you worry now. The Guardian Knights
will maintain the peace in this town.
That looks delicious.
Yeah, it's very fresh.
For a pretty priestess like you,
I'll toss in another one for free.
Oh? Are you sure?
Sure! Take it.
Thank you very much.
May the holy light protect you.
Frey.
Kasel.
I'm so glad I ran into you.
I haven't seen you in a while.
I was wondering how you were doing.
Don't worry about me.
I'm doing fine, and Clause is with me.
That's good to hear.
I was worried that you'd eat something
strange again and upset your stomach.
When have I ever eaten
anything out of the ordinary?
You always do. Like centipedes, spiders...
There's nothing weird about that.
It is weird.
Remember when we were small, you, me,
and Clause went insect hunting until sundown?
Yeah, we lost track of time and
got dragged back to the orphanage.
The priest was so mad,
both Clause and I cried.
But you just fell asleep, exhausted.
Really?
Yes. Clause was surprised
that you had such nerves of steel.
Kasel, you're working very hard as a knight.
I'm still stuck at the apprentice level, though.
Earlier today...
Well... A little incident happened in town,
but I couldn't stop it.
I see.
Well, you should finish
your apprenticeship soon, and look sharp.
I just want to be a knight
that can protect everyone.
Nothing else matters.
You really don't change, do you?
Please enter.
My king, I have news.
Behl. What is it?
We have received word of
Demon sightings in the King's Forest.
Demons...!
We will send out scouts immediately.
We must not allow
a single Demon to enter Orvelia.
Yes, I understand.
We are not where we were
100 years ago... If they do...
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Lord Moriham.
This person...
He is with me. Let us through.
That's a dark elf.
Yeah...
What are you waiting for?
Y-Yes, sir!
B-But you'll need to hand in your weapon.
Naturally.
Demons in the King's Forest...
Could the Dark Lord's armies be in Orvelia...?
King Kyle destroyed the Dark Lord
a hundred years ago,
in the Battle of Galluah Plains.
That's impossible.
Even if it's not the actual Dark Legion,
we still aren't sure
how many Demons there are.
We have no idea how many men
we would need to investigate this.
Shouldn't we limit the sacrifice to a minimum?
The size of the force to send
should be as small as possible.
If none return to give a report,
that would be completely useless!
Greetings, everyone.
Lord Moriham.
Who is this?
He is my soldier, Chancellor.
But he's a dark elf...!
Why would you let someone like that
into the castle, Lord Moriham?!
There is no law barring dark elves
from entering the castle.
Or...
Did someone commit the unspeakable act
of making rules without the king's consent?
So why did you bring him here?
I have heard that we must
send scouts to investigate this.
These men, the Black Edge,
should be useful to us.
Black Edge...?
A band of fierce mercenaries,
who are growing in fame.
This man, Riheet, the leader of the Black Edge,
can take on 100 men alone.
--What?!
--What...?
I ask you. The animosity between Orvelia
and the dark elves runs deep.
What made you think of lending us aid?
We are men for hire.
I have no interest in who hires me.
I see... And what do you ask,
in return for your aid?
Nothing... Pay us our rewards,
and I ask for nothing else.
They are simple and clear.
That's what makes them trustworthy.
They are quite unlike those who, for example,
claim to work for the nation,
yet concentrate on their own
political or financial gains.
Chancellor, please,
make use of the Black Edge.
We cannot allow these suspicious strangers
to take on such an important mission...
There is no place in the defense
of Orvelia for these dark elves!
I also oppose!
They are all correct.
We will be the ones to defend our nation.
As you wish. My apologies
for speaking out of line.
How can you eat that thing?
I'm getting heartburn just from watching...
Whole-cooked spider is quite delicious.
Kasel eats anything and eats a lot of it.
If nothing else, his stomach is strong.
Yeah, sure...
By the way, I saw Frey earlier.
Frey?
Yeah, bumped into her in the street.
She's gotten very priestly.
I see... Good to hear she's working hard.
Yeah.
Clause is a knight; Frey is a priestess.
You've both made your dreams come true.
Kasel, you'll finish
your apprenticeship in no time, too.
Well, you always say I still
have a long way to go...
I'm changing my educational style.
From now on, it's positive reinforcement.
You should be thankful, Kasel.
Yeah, Clause's training style is a bit harsh.
What an understatement.
Kasel. I'm going off on a new mission.
You won't be training with me for a while.
Huh?
We got word that Demons
were spotted in the King's Forest.
Our squad is being sent to investigate.
Gran and Flegg are going, too.
Make sure to keep training
while we're gone, all right?
Do spiders sound good for your souvenir?
Yes...
Don't look so glum, Kasel.
This is what we knights are for.
Yeah...
Come on, eat up. You're buying tonight!
Again, why me...?
H-Help me!
Sneaking in here was easy!
That went well.
Yeah. You had no trouble
getting inside that castle, Riheet.
Yeah.
So when are we doing this?! We're going to
kill all the rotten nobles, right?
You idiot. Think for a change.
But Tamm is right. If we're
going to do it, we're always ready!
--Yeah!
--Yeah, give us the order, Riheet!
We'll do it! Bring it on!
Shut up.
We just took the first step.
Yeah. We don't want to get
ahead of ourselves and mess this up.
We dark elves have been oppressed
by Orvelia for a hundred years.
We've finally been given the
opportunity to take revenge...!
We follow you.
It'll be fun to see the looks on their faces
when we take control of this nation!
Until then, we'll pretend to be harmless.
So loud...
This whole nation will be ours.
Good, you're keeping up with your training.
I'm just following orders.
Right, orders. I guess it's been a while
since the scouts took off...
They do seem to be taking
longer than they should.
--Yes...
--I wonder if something went wrong.
Clause is with them, I'm sure they're fine.
I don't see any Demons anywhere.
Are we sure those sightings are accurate?
Who knows? It's possible they saw wolves
or something and mistook them as Demons.
That sounds likely. I want to head back
and get something nice to eat...
What's wrong, Clause?
There's something out there.
Prepare for combat.
Let's get out of the forest.
U-Understood!
Are these the Demons?!
Flegg!
I'm fine!
Thanks.
More coming!
Gran!
Stay there!
Flegg!
Gran, can you move?!
Flegg, he's...
I'll hold them here!
You go to the castle and report!
Dammit... Dammit!
Go!
I'm counting on you.
Nobody gets through me!
I-It's terrible!
What is it?
The scouts are back!
But there's only one of them!
Just one?! Why?!
I don't know!
Hey! Kasel!
What happened...?
Did the Demons get them...?
I-I'm here to report...
We encountered Demons in the King's Forest.
Scouts have engaged this threat!
How many Demons were there?
The total number is... unknown...
Hey! Wake up!
Give him medical attention, immediately.
--Yes, sir!
--We must do something...
...or else Demons will enter the capital soon.
We must hold off the Demons,
no matter the cost!
Let us send more men into
the forest to defeat the Demons!
More soldiers would just lead to more deaths.
Besides, now is the time
to conserve our power.
There's a chance we could see a flood
of Demons like 100 years ago.
Then what do you suggest we do...?
Use the manpower I have acquired.
The Black Edge.
We cannot trust the dark elves!
E-Exactly! On our honor,
we cannot accept their aid!
Do not lose sight of what our enemy is.
Our enemies are the Demons.
When our nation is under this grave threat,
we cannot waste time bickering
over differences in race.
Please decide, Chancellor.
Only Gran returned...
So... that's what that means.
I understand how you feel...
but you have to let it go.
Kasel.
Frey, what are you doing here?
I heard the scouts returned, and...
...that only one of them returned...
Only Gran came back.
Clause is safe, right?
I'm sure he is.
That's why I have to go.
Go? Go where?
To find Clause.
That's absurd! Kasel, you're just an apprentice!
If you go all alone, and the Demons attack...
I'm still going! I have to save Clause!
Kasel!
I never want to lose anyone again!
I don't want to let anyone else
I care about die! Never again!
Kasel...
I'm going with you.
--No!
--Yes.
I also don't want to lose anyone dear to me.
Besides, my skills as
a priestess should be useful.
Frey, you need to wait here!
Clause asked me to take care of you.
There is nothing you can say to stop me.
In order to protect those dear to us,
we took off on a journey and left Orvelia.
At our destination, the King's Forest,
we witnessed a sad reality,
and a surprising truth...
"The Truth, Revealed"
we witnessed a sad reality,
and a surprising truth...